<xml>
	<about><![CDATA[I am a senior engineer interactive Flash, ActionScript focus on the development, loving the interactive Flash Web applications, RIA is now increasingly popular, where he is a trend. Site display my past work, you can be seen, most of them in Flash Web case, long-term cooperation and excellent designers, as well as a large number of production experience, I have to learn how to use design to subvert not thinking likely to override the arrogance of the code above, and if they do not personally percussion code, do not advance to say "no"!
<br>Site domain name: <b>www.asflash.cn</b>, my blog domain name:<a href="http://blog.asflasher.cn" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">http://blog.asflasher.cn</font></a>. I hope I can continue the growth of technology to become more and more prominent, three years of programming experience Flash, Flash bias in the application front-end effects. I hope that can do some interesting things, and want to draw a very good platform, I can give full play to their own advantages. If you have any intention of co-operation please enter contact plate .]]></about>
	<contact><![CDATA[<a href="mailto:asflash@126.com"><font color="#ff0000">asflash@126.com</font></a><br><br>Mobile: 17320505853<br><br>Address: Chaoyang District, Beijing, China<br><br>MSN: jxp4531@hotmail.com<br><br>QQ: 33786463<br><br>my blog domain name:<a href="http://blog.asflasher.cn" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">http://blog.asflasher.cn</font></a><br>]]></contact>

	<works>
       <title>THE TRAINING OF THE 360 COMPANY'S NEW STUDENTS </title>
       <info><![CDATA[THE TRAINING OF THE 360 COMPANY'S NEW STUDENTS <br><br>Click into the site: <a href="https://jxp4531.github.io/flashgame/works/sites/360train" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">works/sites/360train</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="526">photos/360train/0.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	<works>
       <title>CHENG XINDONG SPACE FOR CONTEMPORARY ART</title>
       <info><![CDATA[CHENG XINDONG SPACE FOR CONTEMPORARY ART,this is a demo!<br><br>Click into the site: <a href="https://jxp4531.github.io/flashgame/works/sites/chengxindong" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">works/sites/chengxindong</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="584">photos/chengxindong/0.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	<works>
       <title>REN JUN STUDIO RELEASED</title>
       <info><![CDATA[Ren Jun, Chinese cities are outstanding representatives of community sculpture, works across a number of cities in China, has participated in domestic and international public art, forums and exchange activities. Powered by Ren Jun, including a number of works, works of the integrated features, using Flash technology development, and has won praise!<br><br>Click into the site: <a href="https://jxp4531.github.io/flashgame/works/sites/renjun/" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">works/sites/renjun</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="585">photos/renjun/0.jpg</image>
		<image h="585">photos/renjun/1.jpg</image>
		<image h="560">photos/renjun/2.jpg</image>
		<image h="578">photos/renjun/3.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	<works>
       <title>ASFLASH 2007 VERSION OF THE DEMO</title>
       <info><![CDATA[asflash 2007 the demo version, this version totally imitate a foreign production site to learn from, the following is a screenshot site!<br><br>Click into the site: <a href="https://jxp4531.github.io/flashgame/works/sites/2007demo/" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">works/sites/2007demo</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="548">photos/2007demo/0.jpg</image>
		<image h="566">photos/2007demo/1.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	<works>
       <title>ZRONG SITE OF THE DEMO SHOW</title>
       <info><![CDATA[Powered by a foreign country, an image display system, cool application. The picture here feeling very happy, for some art design picture of the application site!<br><br>Click into the site: <a href="https://jxp4531.github.io/flashgame/works/sites/zrong/" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">works/sites/zrong</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="575">photos/zrong/0.jpg</image>
		<image h="600">photos/zrong/1.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	<works>
       <title>CCTV.COM DANCE COMPETITIONS TO THE OFFICIAL WEBSITE</title>
       <info><![CDATA[cctv.com dance competitions to the official website, the website covers a dynamic form, the dynamic performance of the film to various forms of dance, lively and interesting!<br><br>Click into the site: <a href="http://ent.cctv.com/special/dance/15/index.shtml" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">http://ent.cctv.com/special/dance/15/index.shtml</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="591">photos/dance/0.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	<works>
       <title>VNOISE COMPANIES DISPLAY CASES</title>
       <info><![CDATA[VNOISE companies, professional production companies of the interactive web site, I have done for the company technical support, inside the case through most of my development of production, of course, is the technical aspects!<br><br>Click into the site: <a href="http://www.v-noise.com" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">http://www.v-noise.com</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="552">photos/vnoise/0.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	<works>
       <title>IN 2005 THE DEVELOPMENT OF CASUAL GAMES SITE,RECOMMENDED</title>
       <info><![CDATA[2005 works, then the purpose is to learn Flash, and love the game Xuanyuan Jian, began to do this site. At that time, there is no new technology, but their level is not high, is too much content. This site on-line, many gamers have been agreed with the permission, they consider this site very interesting, the site of the screen are from games, drama and procedures set by me to complete. Spent about two months, while learning side of things to do. I am a love game players. In fact, this is not the real game, that is, casual use!<br><br>Click into the site: <a href="https://jxp4531.github.io/flashgame/works/sites/flash" target="blank"><font color="#ff0000">works/sites/flash</font></a>]]></info>
       <image>
        <image h="567">photos/flash/0.jpg</image>
		<image h="562">photos/flash/1.jpg</image>
		<image h="563">photos/flash/2.jpg</image>
		<image h="561">photos/flash/3.jpg</image>
		<image h="562">photos/flash/4.jpg</image>
		<image h="560">photos/flash/5.jpg</image>
		<image h="561">photos/flash/6.jpg</image>
		<image h="561">photos/flash/7.jpg</image>
		</image>
	</works>
	
</xml>
